氦
Helium.
没错
Yes.
泰勒·斯威夫特
Taylor Swift.
没错
Yes.
π
Pi.
对
Yes.
卡戴珊
Kardashian.
哪一个
More specific.
科勒
Khloe?
对了
Yes!
我能记得是因为  长得像金就是金·卡戴珊
See, I remembered because if it looks like Kim it's Kim,
如果长得有点像金  那就是葛妮
if it looks kind of like Kim it's Kourtney,
如果长得完全不像金  那就是科勒
and if it looks nothing like Kim it's Khloe.
这是维恩图解
Oh, that's a Venn Diagram,
我能记得是因为我当时想
and I remember because I thought to myself,
"这叫维恩的家伙  什么时候能不说这图了"
"Venn is he gonna stop talking about this diagram?"
你们俩在干嘛
What are you guys doing?
我们决定用我们早餐时间
Oh, well, we decided to use our breakfast time
来扩大我们各自的知识储备
to expand our respective knowledge bases.
让我试试
Oh, let me try.
氢原子与魔力红的主唱亚当[两者音似]
Hmm, atom of hydrogen, Adam of Maroon 5,
扔麦霸气退场
mic drop.
抱歉  谁是扔麦霸·气退场
I'm sorry, who is Mike Drop?
佩妮  你晚点想跟我一起
Oh, hey, Penny, do you want to go to the airport
去机场接我妈吗
with me later to pick up my mother?
-好啊  -谢谢
- Sure. - Thanks.
-小事  -佩妮
- No problem. - Hey, Penny,
既然你都要去机场了
um, since you're already gonna be at the airport,
我还有去的必要吗
do I need to go?
你为什么不想去机场接你妈妈
Why don't you want to get your mother from the airport?
因为我的人生不需要增加一段
Well, I can do without the 40-minute car ride
对我人生长达40分钟的全方位嘲讽
where she criticizes every aspect of my life.
她一趟车程就能全说完了吗
She can cover it in a car ride?
光是你的姿势我就能说40分钟呢
I could do 40 minutes on your posture alone.
你真的想要我一个人去接你妈吗
You really want me to pick up your mother all by myself?
我只是觉得
Hmm, I just feel like
这是你们俩增进感情的好机会
it would be a good chance for you to bond.
或是你避开她的好机会吗
Or a way for you to avoid her?
我不知道他的卡上都写了什么
I don't know what he's putting on those cards,
但你机智程度破了你人生记录啊
but you are smarter than ever.
如果真想我去  那我就去接你妈妈吧
Fine, if you really want me to, I will pick your mom up.
真的吗
Seriously?
对啊  毕竟她也是我婆婆
Yeah, you know what, she is my mother-in-law,
我也想我们能好好相处
and I'd like for us to have a good relationship.
你这行为好成熟
That is very mature of you,
所以我决定告诉你  "傻逼"
so I'm gonna go ahead and say, "Suckah."
-继续学习  -好的
- All right, back to learning. - Okay.
简单  《比尔教科学》的主持人比尔
Oh, easy, Bill Nye the Science Guy.
我印象中的他是...
Or as I know him...
"《与星共舞》里的怪老头"
"Creepy old dude from Dancing with the Stars."
你们知道最近有场《复仇者联盟》的放映吗
Did you guys see there's an Avengers screening?
这戏的导演会放出删减的片段
Joss Whedon's gonna show some deleted scenes
还会有一个问与答的环节
and do a question and answer session.
我对于上一部《复仇者联盟》电影
Oh, well, I have a few questions for him
有几个问题想问他
about the last Avengers movie...
还有一大堆吐槽答案
and a whole lot of answers.
活动是什么时候
When's the screening?
今晚  但是谁先来谁有座
Uh, it's tonight, but it's first-come, first-served,
所以我们应该提早去排队
so we should probably get there early and wait in line.
咱们去吧
Let's do it.
佩妮得忙着陪我妈妈  我也去
Penny's busy with my mother, so I'm in.
有个坏消息
Oh, bad news.
艾米叫我晚点陪她去逛街
Amy's making me go shopping with her later,
所以大家都别想去了
so looks like none of us can go.
你知道你不在场时我们也有权享乐的吧
You do realize we're allowed to have fun without you?
通常就是因为你不在才能享乐
In fact, that's usually the trick to it.
我们几点得到
What time do we need to get there?
我觉得3点吧
Uh, I'd say by 3:00.
你们真的要抛下我去玩吗
You're really going without me?
不是什么大事
It's not a big deal.
去跟艾米逛街吧
Go shopping with Amy,
到时候我们帮你占一个位置
and we'll save a spot in line for you.
你没有权利在队伍中帮人占位置
You don't have the authority to save places in the line.
如果我这么做  那就是插队了
If I do that, I'll be cutting.
大家都这样啊
People do it all the time.
你知道排队的黄金条例
You know the golden rule of line etiquette:
"插队死全家"
"No cuts, no buts, no coconuts."
如果你真这么在意
If you really care that much,
现在也有很多软件可以让你花钱请人
there are apps now that'll let you hire people to do stuff
代跑腿或者代排队啊
like errands and wait in lines.
真有人的工作是排队吗
People are actually waiting in lines as a job?
突然对自己的人生产生满足感
Boy, makes me feel better about my life.
他们其中有些人时薪超过20块呢
Some of these guys make over $20 an hour.
现在我又悲伤感爆棚了
And now I feel worse again.
我一点都不惊讶莱纳德选择逃避接机
I'm not surprised Leonard chose to avoid picking me up.
他这辈子都在克服亲密关系问题
He's battled intimacy issues his whole life.
他对于保持勃起状态会有困难吗
Does he have difficulty maintaining erections?
都还没开出停车场呢
Didn't even make it out of the parking lot.
莱纳德的事说够多了
Uh, you know what, enough about Leonard.
来说说你的事吧
Let's talk about you.
你这次来这里  有想做什么吗
What would you like to do while you're here?
亲爱的  我是个心理医生
Dear, I'm a psychiatrist.
你不用逃避跟我谈论私密的话题
You don't have to avoid having intimate conversations with me.
其实我也想跟你变得亲近
Well, I'd actually like for us to be close,
或许我们可以聊聊我们最喜欢的书
but maybe we start with our favorite books
然后再慢慢聊到我丈夫的性器官
and work our way up to my husband's sex organs.
没问题
Very well.
你最近读的一本书是什么
What's the last book you read?
家具店春季目录算吗
Um, does Pottery Barn, Spring count?
佩妮  想要自己的婆婆喜欢自己很正常
Penny, it's only natural to want your mother-in-law to like you,
我承认我有时过于强势吓人
and I acknowledge I can be an intimidating person.
我该怎么做才能让你自在点呢
So what can I do to make this process easier for you?
比如说
Uh, for starters,
你能不能不要跟我玩精神分析这一套
maybe you can not psychoanalyze everything I say?
那当我精神分析你时
And how does it make you feel
你有什么感觉呢
when I psychoanalyze everything you say?
很不舒服
Uncomfortable.
亲爱的  我刚才在开玩笑
That was a joke, dear.
抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
不知道你还会开玩笑
Didn't know you made those.
不如我们今晚来个
Hey, listen, what if we have a little
婆媳小聚餐吧
mother-in-law-daughter-in-law dinner tonight?
所以就咱俩吗
So just the two of us?
或许我再叫上俩闺蜜
Or I invite a few girlfriends,
因为听到你说"就咱俩"时
'cause hearing you say "The two of us"
我的后脊一阵发凉
just sent a chill right down my spine.
你上车干嘛
What are you doing here?
你又不是谢尔顿
You're not Sheldon.
我早料到你可能会这么说
I thought that might come up.
谢尔顿花钱雇我  让我跟你去逛街
Sheldon hired me to go shopping with you.
慢着
Hold on.
他给你钱  好不用跟我一起待着是吗
He paid you to get out of spending time with me?
不  不是那样的
No, it's not like that.
是他宁可去排一条长长的队
There's a long line he'd rather stand in.
我们要做什么  你想买衣服还是做玩具熊
So what are we doing? Old Navy, Build-A-Bear?
反正做啥我都有钱拿
I get paid either way.
我才不会跟你去逛街
We're not going shopping together.
你确定吗  我可是很乐意帮你拿包包哦
You sure? I'm happy to hold your bag.
谢尔顿还给了我买热狗棒的钱
And Sheldon gave me money for a hotdog on a stick.
你能理解为什么我现在很火大吗
Can you understand why I might be annoyed right now?
女士  我今天才第一天上班
Look, lady, I just work here.
我们一起排过很多次队  对吧
We've waited in a lot of lines together, haven't we?
还记得我们为了漫展
Remember when we camped out
《神秘博士》的剧组在外露营了吗
for the Doctor Who panel at Comic-Con?
记得  露宿在星空下
Yeah, sleeping under the stars
跟一群像我们一样热爱这部剧的粉丝们
with other fans who love the show as much as we do.
醒来后寻思  到底是哪个粉丝偷了我们的钱包
Waking up, wondering which one of those fans stole our wallets.
斯尔图特  你来这里干嘛
Stuart, what are you doing here?
谢尔顿  你是我这辈子见过
Sheldon, you are the most inconsiderate person
最不顾及别人感受的人
I have ever met in my entire life!
你哪儿来的胆子  居然让我
Where do you get off sending me
去陪你女朋友逛街
to shop with your girlfriend?!
我糊涂了
I don't understand.
之前给你钱时  你不是很乐意这么做吗
You were happy to do this when I hired you.
为什么现在对我这么不爽
Why-why are you upset with me now?
不是我对你不爽  但艾米现在超级不爽你
Oh, I'm not upset with you, but Amy's pretty bent out of shape,
所以她花钱请我来骂你
so she hired me to let you have it.
天道好轮回  苍天饶过谁
Well, I suppose turnabout is fair play.
你他妈说对了  你个自私的混蛋
You're darn right it's fair play, you selfish jerk!
正当我觉得
You know, just when I think
我们的关系取得进展时
we're making progress in our relationship,
我们又恢复原状
we revert to our old patterns
他有什么想法和情绪都不告诉我
where thoughts and feelings go unexpressed.
我是说  如果他不想跟我去逛街
I mean, if he didn't want to go shopping with me,
那他干嘛不直接说
why didn't he just say so?
或许是因为他插不上嘴
Maybe he couldn't get a word in edgewise.
抱歉  我一直喋喋不休
I'm sorry, I've been going on and on.
没关系  亲爱的
Oh, it's all right, dear.
谢尔顿的大脑睿智又复杂
Sheldon has a brilliant and complicated mind.
我可以理解跟他谈恋爱
It's understandable that being in a relationship with him
会比较费劲
could be trying.
我有次叫了他"宝贝"
I called him "babe" once.
他怀疑我嗑药  要我药检
He asked me to get a drug test.
我真的很佩服你的决心
Well, I do admire your resolve.
-你是一名非凡的女性  -谢谢
- You're an extraordinary woman. - Thank you.
她是我婆婆
You know, she's my mother-in-law.
为什么我不能跟她像这样热络呢
Why can't I bond with her like that?
艾米跟她视如己出的谢尔顿在一起
Amy's with Sheldon who she loves like a son.
而你跟她...
You're with her son...
视如外人的儿子在一起
who she doesn't.
你知道我们谈了五年  他才愿意给我做按摩吗
Do you realize it took me five years to get a massage from him?
那对谢尔顿来说  也算是很大的进步了
Oh, well, that still could be a big step for Sheldon.
三分钟
Three minutes.
他用了一个厨房计时器计时
And he used a kitchen timer.
我觉得自己就像一颗溏心蛋
I felt like a soft-boiled egg.
跟莱纳德一起相处
You know, being in a relationship with Leonard
也是挑战满满哦
also comes with its challenges.
是啊
Yes.
但你又能怎么样呢
Well, what can you do?
或许是谢尔顿来道歉了
Maybe it's Sheldon, here to say he's sorry.
谢尔顿说对不起
Sheldon says he's sorry.
伯纳黛特  我给你五块钱  使劲摔门
Bernadette, I'll give you five dollars to slam the door.
我收三块就行
I would have done it for three.
天啊  站这么久我好累啊
Boy, all this standing's making me tired.
还好我带了我的手杖折叠椅
Good thing I brought my collapsible stick chair.
我讨厌那椅子
Not the stick chair.
你坐在那玩意上像个傻子
You look like an idiot on that thing.
棍杖和石头或许会弄断我的骨头
Sticks and stones may break my bones,
但在棍杖上的椅子  超舒服哦
but chairs on sticks are comfy.
艾米的事摆平了吗
Is everything smoothed out with Amy?
没有  她还是很生气
Uh, no, she's still pretty mad.
你道歉的时候  有像我那样真诚吗
Did you make the apology as sincere as I would have?
我说"谢尔顿说对不起"
I said, "Sheldon says he's sorry."
那有点过分真诚了
Oh, well, that's laying it on a little thick.
你该亲自去跟她道歉了吧
You think it's time you apologize to her yourself?
我想也是
I suppose so.
但如果我走出队伍  我的位置就没了
But if I get out of the line, I'll lose my spot.
我很乐意帮你保留位置等你回来
I'm happy to hold your place till you get back.
你会这么做吗
You would do that?
就当这是我坑你钱的方式吧
Consider it my way of getting more of your money.
你真是一个好人
You're a good man.
贝弗莉  你知道佩妮
So, Beverly, did you know Penny
是我们制药公司业绩第三名的销售代表吗
is the number three sales rep at our pharmaceutical company?
我都不知道你们俩一起工作
Oh, I didn't realize you two work together.
其实不算是
Well, we don't exactly.
我是研发团队的微生物学家
I'm a microbiologist for the research team.
你们最近在研发什么
Oh, what are you currently developing?
一种抗焦虑的新药
Some exciting new anti-anxiety drugs.
真是巧了
That's interesting.
我刚参加了一个关于儿童焦虑症的讲座
I just attended a lecture on pediatric anxiety.
是不是杰诺夫斯基博士的讲座
Oh, was it, uh, Dr. Jenofski?
我才看了他的TED演讲
I just saw his TED Talk!
正是他的
It was.
我们还是聊回佩妮吧
Let's get back to Penny.
对了  你之前不是提起过
Hey, weren't you telling me
公司给你的那辆车有多棒吗
something great about your company car?
车上有座椅加热器
It has seat warmers.
艾米  艾米
Amy! Amy!
-艾米  -进来
- Amy! - Come in.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
贝弗利  很高兴见到你
Oh, Beverly, good to see you!
我本想坐下来小聊一下  但是
I'd love to chat, but there's a line
我们排的队马上就要进场了  所以我就直说了
that could start moving any minute, so let's do this.
艾米
Amy?
一个完整的道歉需要以下三个步骤
A proper apology requires three steps.
第一步  承认错误
Step one-- an admission of wrongdoing.
艾米  我错了
Amy, I was wrong.
第二步
Step two--
承诺再也不犯同样的错误
a promise never to repeat said action.
艾米  我再也不会犯同样的错了
Amy, that action will never be repeated,
我保证
and that's a promise.
第三步  诚恳地请求对方原谅
Step three-- an earnest request for forgiveness.
艾米  求求你原谅我吧
Amy, I hope you can forgive me.
而且你最好快点原谅
And I hope you do it right now,
因为还有辆优步在楼下等着我呢
'cause there's an Uber waiting downstairs,
我可不想对着我的司机甘尼什
and I don't want to repeat this apology nonsense
再重复一遍无聊的道歉了
with my driver Ganesh.
原谅你了
Fine.
多谢了  你真是个好人
Oh, thanks! You're a peach!
贝弗利  回聊啊
Beverly, we'll catch up soon.
伯纳黛特  回见啊
Bernadette, it was a pleasure as always,
佩妮  你牙齿上有菠菜
Penny, you have spinach in your teeth.
这菠菜粘在我牙齿上多久了
How long have I had spinach in my teeth?
在机场时就有了  亲
Since the airport, dear.
你看起来就像是长了个支架一样
You look like you come with a kickstand.
你的话伤不了我
You can't make me feel bad.
也许我不行  莱纳德你来
Hmm, maybe not. Leonard?
外星人把你送回来时
So, when the aliens brought you back,
是不是忘记把探测仪拔出来了
they just left the probe in?
我回来了
I'm back.
-怎么样  -完美
- Hey, how'd it go? - It went well.
我发现如果你从来没有道过歉
Yeah, I've learned that if you never say you're sorry,
当你真的道歉时  对方可是会吓到呢
the times you do really puts them on their heels.
斯图尔特  你可以不用帮我排队了
Uh, Stuart, I relieve you of your line duties.
还有人需要我的帮忙吗
Anyone else need anything before I go?
给你一块钱  羞辱一下拉杰
I'll give you a dollar if make fun of Raj.
-你太坏了  -五块钱
- That's mean. - Five.
你好像长着尾巴的跳跳虎
You look like Tigger
如果跳跳虎和你一样像个智障的话
if Tigger looked like a jackass.
如果你以后需要推荐人
Uh, if you ever need a reference or anything,
记得找我
just let me know.
我来了
Hey, guys.
你总算赶到了
You made it.
你们看见没
Did you see that?
他插队了
He just cut the line.
人家有朋友在排队呢  别管了
He's just joining his friends; it's fine.
不  我才不能不管
No, it's not fine.
这破坏了排队的规则
It is a breach of line etiquette.
我们差不多排在队伍的最前面了
We're near the front of the line.
不管怎样我们都能进去
We'll get in either way.
如果我们之前的每个人都让人插队呢
What if every person in front of us lets someone cut?
我们也能进去
We'd still get in.
如果每个插队的人又让人插队呢
What if each of those people let someone cut?
还是能进去
Still get in.
如果后来的人又让人插队呢
But then each of those people let someone cut?
还是能进去  但首先
We'd still get in, but first I'd hit you
我要用他的手杖椅把你打昏
over the head with his stick chair.
-对不起  -求你别说
- Excuse me. - Oh, please don't.
我看到
Uh, uh, I couldn't help but notice
你插队了
that you cut the line.
我朋友在这排着呢
Oh, uh, I'm with my friends.
没事
It's cool.
才怪
Well, no.
这才不会没事
It's not cool.
如果座位是预定好的
If there were reserved seating,
我们每个人都有票  那就没事
and we all had tickets, that would be fine.
但这队伍是谁先来谁有座
But this line is first-come, first-served.
而不是"最后一个来  最先一个坐"
Not "Show up tardy and nevertheless be first served"
来击个掌吧
Right here.
不要
No.
你得站到队伍最后面去
You need to go to the back of the line.
谁批准你来当排队监督员的
Uh, who made you line monitor?
小学四年级的旺琪老师
Mrs. Wunch in fourth grade.
我的口号是"笔直的队伍
And my slogan was "A line that's straight
才是好队伍"
is a line that's great""
这家伙是认真的吗
Is this guy for real?
老兄  我也希望他是在开玩笑
Boy, I wish I could say no.
谢尔顿愿意道歉  真是很不错
That was very nice of Sheldon to apologize.
他已经进步很多了
Well, he's come a long way.
或者是慢慢进小碎步
Or a short way very slowly,
所以让人错觉已经是很大的进步了
so it feels like a long way.
你和他之间的关系真是太有意思了
Your relationship with him is fascinating.
我正准备写一本有关那些事业有成的伴侣的书
I'm preparing to write a book on high-achieving couples,
我很想采访一下你们
and I would love to interview the both of you.
好啊
Oh, sure.
我会告诉谢尔顿这事
I'll-I'll talk to Sheldon about it.
伯纳黛特的老公以前还当过宇航员呢
You know, Bernadette's husband is a former astronaut.
真的吗
Really?
你觉得他会对
Do you think he would be interested
被采访感兴趣吗
in being interviewed as well?
我觉得他会感兴趣吗
Do I think he'd be interested?
有时候我能听到他独自躲在厕所里
Sometimes I hear him pretending to be interviewed
假装正在接受采访呢
when he's alone in the bathroom.
太好了
Wonderful!
我会把联系方式留给你
I'll give you my contact information.
你也应该和佩妮聊聊啊
Um, you should probably talk to Penny, too.
聊什么
About what?
你知道吗
Okay, you know what?
你真是太奇葩了
This is ridiculous.
我这一天都努力跟你处好关系
I've been trying to make a connection with you all day,
明显都是白费力
and clearly I'm getting nowhere.
你是在寻求相互有种默契
Well, are you seeking a connection
还是某种形式的承认
or just some form of validation?
我在寻求的是一点友情
What I was seeking was some sort of friendship.
但走到这步  我只求你不当面羞辱我就好
But at this point, I'll take you not insulting me to my face.
我的本意从不是要羞辱你
My intention was never to insult you.
你今天一整天都是这样
You've been doing it all day!
你到底知不知道什么是羞辱
Do you even know what an insult is?!
虽然不是临床用语
Well, it's not a clinical term.
但举个例子  应该是你嫁给我儿子
But one example would be your marrying my son,
没有邀请也没有告知我
and not inviting me or even telling me
要结婚这件事
the wedding was taking place.
好  这个例子好
Okay, good example.
乔斯·惠登的作品是如何令你觉得
What about Joss Whedon's work makes you think he'd be okay
破坏规则和插队是没问题的
with rule-breakers and line-cutters?!
复仇者联盟就是破坏规则者
The Avengers are rule-breakers!
复仇二字就写在职责描述里
Being vengeful is in their job description!
他们为神盾局工作
They work for SHIELD,
那是受美国政府管理的部门
which is a sanctioned department of the U.S. Government!
你也为受美国政府管理的部门工作吗
Do you work for a sanctioned department of the U.S. Government?
其实我还真是
As a matter of fact I do.
在一个小地方叫"车辆管理局"
At a little place called the DMV.
他说得有道理
He's got him there.
而且跟神盾局一样有"局"字
The D even stands for department.
大家注意
Excuse me!
大家看这里  能不能举手表态
Excuse me, can I please see a show of hands?
认为此人插队行为有问题的请举手
Who here takes issue with this person cutting the line?
我就说吧
Told you.
多么悲哀的世道啊
Well, what a sad state of affairs!
你们都被生活打击到
That you've all been so ground down by life,
连有人不尊重你们都毫无知觉
you don't even notice when someone disrespects you.
不敢相信我们即将被揍的原因
I can't believe we're gonna get beat up,
居然不是因为你的手杖椅
and it's not because of your chair.
可知道就在现在  队伍的后面
You know, right now, at the back of this line,
有一个和你一样的影迷
there's a movie fan like you
即将无法进入影厅
who's not going to get in,
就是因为这个人的不在乎
because this person simply doesn't care.
没错  在61年前的队伍里
Yeah, well, 61 years ago,
后面也站着一个人
there was another person at the back of the line
美国五六十年代的女性黑人民权运动者
因为拒绝公车司机要求黑人给白人让座的要求而被捕
她的名字就叫罗莎·帕克斯
and her name was Rosa Parks.
听着  你一会儿可能要装成黑人
Okay, you may have to pretend you're black
帮我们逃过这一劫
to get us out of here.
现在让我们跟随那位勇敢女性的脚步
Now, let's follow in that brave woman's footsteps,
为我们自己站出来吧
and stand up for ourselves!
我知道她是为了能坐下而"站起来"的
And-and I realize that she stood up by remaining seated,
但现在不是享受这份讽刺感的时候
but now is not that time to enjoy the irony of that.
现在我再问一遍
Now, I ask you again.
如果你觉得这个人...
Who here takes issue with this person--?
我们为什么要听你讲话  你也是一个插队的
Why should we listen to you? You cut the line yourself.
我确定一定以及肯定没有
I most certainly did not.
我亲眼看到的
I saw you.
如果你觉得头晕
If you're feeling dizzy,
那是因为风水轮流转
it's because the tables have turned.
你听好  我是付钱请人替我排队
Excuse me, I paid someone to wait in line for me,
等我到达以后  他就走了
and then when I arrived, he left,
所以你这女子亲眼所见的
so what you saw, my good woman,
叫"换"人  不叫"插"队
was "swapsies" not "cutsies"
不行不行  等等
Oh, no, no, no, no, wait!
我再问一遍  请举手
I ask you all again. A show of hands.
谁对这个人...  别走了
Who here takes issue--? Well, stop moving!
他就要进去了
He's gonna get in!
-兄弟  随他吧  -不行  我做不到
- Buddy, let it go. - No, I can't.
这样不对
This isn't right.
你已经尽力了
You did everything you could.
不  我还能更努力
No, I could've done more.
乖啦  你把我们对伟大人权运动先驱的
Now, now, you denigrated the memory
美好记忆都摧毁了
of a great civil rights pioneer.
你做的已经够多了
That's all anyone could ask.
老实说  我没有想到你居然会在乎那场婚礼
To be honest, I'm surprised you cared about the wedding at all.
我也是个人  佩妮
I'm still human, Penny.
自己儿子的婚礼不被邀请
Not getting invited to my own son's wedding
很难不在意
is difficult to ignore.
我懂你的感受
I know how you feel.
她也没有邀请我们
She didn't invite any of us.
那是一时冲动下去结的
It was spur of the moment!
但我们有在网上看直播
But we did get to see a live stream of it on the Internet.
我也可以看网上直播啊
I could've watched it on the Internet?
谢你啊
Thank you.
所以如果我们邀请你去拉斯维加斯
So if we would have asked you to come to Vegas
参加我们的婚礼  你会来的吗
to see us get married, you would've come?
不会  我会说你们犯了滔天大错
No, I would've said you're making a huge mistake.
但邀请一下也算礼数做到了啊
But an invitation would've been nice.
你真觉得我们是错误吗
You really think we made a mistake?
当时我是那么认为的
At the time I did.
但我从来没见过莱纳德那么开心
But I-I've never seen Leonard so happy,
所以  也许是我错了
so... perhaps I was wrong.
好吧
Okay.
那这样吧
Well, um, how about this?
趁着你还在城里
Maybe while you're still in town,
我跟莱纳德再办一次小仪式
Leonard and I could have another small ceremony.
如果你想参加的话
You know, if you're interested.
我完全可以接受
I would find that perfectly acceptable.
她说完全可以接受
She would find it perfectly acceptable!
你们看到了吧  我们婆媳情深
You guys saw it! We bonded!
华仔  你没事吧
Howie? You doing okay?
你已经在里面待很久了
You've been in there a while.
没事  马上出去
I'm fine. Be right out.
我算不算美国英雄
Am I an American hero?
真是个好问题  吉姆
Well, that's a good question, Jim.
你不觉得一位宇航员一旦离开了地球
Don't you think once an astronaut leaves the planet,
就成为世界英雄了吗
he's a hero to all the nations of the Earth?
好的
Okey dokey.
我应该还有空回答最后一道问题
I think I have time for one more question.